Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
- U.S. Air Force Academy (AFA)
  - Specifications and Correspondence
    - Correspondence with Air Force Academy #4 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence with Air Force Academy #3 (Box 130)
    - Report (Box 130)
    - Office Furniture Cost Estimate (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings Cadet Quarters, Cadet Rooms, U.S. Air Force Academy (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings Cadet Quarters Cadet Rooms, US Air Force Academy (Box 131)
    - Valet Unit Cost Estimates Cadet Quarters, Cadet Room (Box 131)
    - Recommend List of Standard T/A Type Items. Commandant of Cadets Headquarters (Box 131)
    - 3rd Floor (Box 131)
    - Cost Analysis Furniture and Office Equipment vs. Cost of Building (Box 131)
    - Office Furniture Cost Estimate (Box 131)
    - Cadet Quarters Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings Cadet Quarters Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Class "B" Special Design Standards, Class "B" Steel Furniture Standards, US Air Force Academy Colorado Springs, Colorado (Box 131)
    - Coffee Service for Academy Superintendent at the Interim Site. Cost Estimate (Box 131)
    - Valet Unit Cost Estimate Cadet Quarters (Box 131)
    - Commandant of Cadet's Headquarters Third Floor (Box 131)
    - Cadet Quarters Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Class "B" Special Design Standards, Class "B" Steel Furniture Standards, US Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colorado (Box 131)
    - Office Furniture Cost Estimate (Box 131)
    - Cost Analysis Furniture and Office Equipment vs. Cost of Building (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings, Cadet Quarters, Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings, Cadet Quarters, Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings, Cadet Quarters, Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Class "B" Special Design Standards, Class "B" Steel Furniture Standards, US Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colorado (Box 131)
    - Office Furniture Cost Estimate (Box 131)
    - Cadet Quarters, Cadet Rooms (Box 131)
    - Budget Estimate for Furnishings, cadet quarters, cadet rooms (Box 131)
    - Receiving & Shipping Tickets, Drawings and Specifications. AFA-1&2. #1 (Box 131)
    - Receiving & Shipping Tickets, Drawings & Specifications. AFA-1&2. #2 (Box 131)
    - Receiving & Shipping Tickets, Drawings & Specifications. AFA-1, 2, &3A. Folder # 3 (Box 132)
    - Shipping Tickets (NY) AFA-1A (Box 132)
    - Receiving Tickets # 2 AFA-1-A 1053 (Box 132)
    - March 1, 1957 - August 31, 1957 (Box 133)
    - January 1, 1958 - January 31, 1958 (Box 133)
    - HB-NY Log - Correspondence - AFA-1, 2, 3, &4A (Box 133)
    - Feb 1, 1958 - Feb 28, 1958 (Box 133)
    - HB-NY Log - AFA-1-2-3&4A., January 1, 1958 through January 31, 1958 (Box 134)
    - HB-NY Log - AFA-1, 2, 3 &4A., February 1, 1958 through February 28, 1958 (Box 134)
    - April 1, 1958 - April 30, 1958 (Box 134)
    - HB-NY Log AFA-1, 2, 3, & 4A (Box 135)
    - AFA - Chicago Office (Box 135)
    - AFA - Chicago - Correspondence to and from (Box 135)
    - AFA - Chicago - Conference Reports, Memos, etc. To & From (Box 136)
    - AFA - Question and Answer Memo - re: Outside Professional Assistance, Especially Industrial Designers - 1 December 1955 (Box 136)
    - AFA - Denver - Correspondence to & from (Box 136)
    - AFA Denver Conf Reports, Memos, From Jan 1958. #6 (Box 136)
    - AFA - Denver Conf Reports, memos, from 7/1/57 to December 1957. Folder # 5 (Box 136)
    - AFA - Denver Conf Reports, Memos, from 2/19/57 to 6/30/57. Folder # 4 (Box 136)
    - AFA - Conference Reports, Memos - Internal. 3. (Box 136)
    - Correspondence with Air Force Academy (Box 137)
    - AFA - Denver Conference Reports, Memos, from 10/15/56 to 2/15/57. Folder #3 (Box 137)
    - Index to Design Directives - Alphabetical (Box 137)
    - Mattress G 113 (Box 137)
    - Procurement Data Sheets (Box 137)
    - Proc. Data Sheets, Rec. Lat. IFB, Memos, etc. (Box 137)
    - Extra Copies - Procurement Data Information (Box 137)
    - Extra Copies - Memos to DCS/M - Procurement Data Info (Box 138)
    - IFB & Specifications (Box 138)
    - Transmittal Letters (Box 138)
    - Equipping Standards (Box 138)
    - ES (Box 138)
    - Definitives - Def. Deliveries, Flimels, Etc. Def. Flimels - Cat. Sheets Destroyed (Box 138)
    - IFB File (IFBs & IFB Correspondence (Box 138)
    - Definitives - Deliveries (Box 138)
    - HB - NY Log - Flimels (Box 138)
    - Definitives, Flimels, Catalog Sheets, Destroyed, Record of (Box 138)
    - IFB Specifications - Spares (Box 138)
    - Chg. Letters & tl memos (Box 138)
    - TL Correspondence File other than Tltrs - Memos, chgs. Etc (Box 138)
    - Ritter Sterilizer RD-5 Obsolete Prints for record (Box 139)
    - Ames Company, WR (Box 139)
    - Architectural Fixture Corp (Box 139)
    - Blau & Sons, Max (Box 139)
    - Architectural Metalcrafts Corp (Box 139)
    - Vendors (Box 139)
    - DHD File - CM-2. 2 Design Data (Box 139)
    - DHD File - CM-2 3-Budget Data (Box 139)
    - DHD File - Cm-2 4-Purchase Orders (Box 139)
    - DHD File - CM-2 1-Correspondence & Conference Reports (Box 139)
    - DHD File - RD-13 1-Correspondence & Budget Miscellaneous (Box 139)
    - DHD File - RD-9 1-Correspondence and Conference Reports (Box 139)
    - RD-14 - DHD File. Correspondence - Budget - Purchase Orders (Box 139)
    - DHD File - RD-9 - 2-Design Data (Box 139)
    - DHD File - RD-9 3-Budget Data (Box 139)
    - DHD File - RD-9 4-Purchase Orders (Box 139)
    - Interoffice Procedure AFA-1-A Binder (Box 140)
    - Progress Reports and Pertinent Information (Box 140)
    - Coffee Service for the Academy Superintendent At the Interim Site Cost Estimate Project no. AFA-1-A (Box 140)
    - "B" Steel - Finished (Box 140)
    - Catalogs of Manufacturers Under Federal Supply Listings (Box 140)
    - IBM Time Equipment and Recorders and clocks and Signals (Box 140)
    - AIA Document No. 172 Standard Filing System and Alphabetical Index (Box 140)
    - Bidders List AFA-2 E-way (Box 140)
    - AFA-1&2 Bid Folder - General (Box 140)
    - AFA-1 F l i l Bids an Library Stacks and Furniture (Box 140)
    - Bids Received (Box 140)
    - AFA-2-F117-F118 Bids Folder (Box 140)
    - Lav AFA G113 (Box 140)
    - AFA-1 G-113 Bids Cadet Room (Box 140)
    - Request for Bid's Folder Dining Hall (Box 140)
    - Books & Manuals Index (Box 141)
    - Barricks Manufacturing Co. (Box 141)
    - Unlabeled Folders (Box 141)
    - AFA-3-P 117 Staff Club Furnishings. E-Way for JW Lee - NY File (Box 142)
    - Specifications - Library Equipment List (Box 142)
    - AFA - Commandant's Headquarters (Box 142)
    - WDTA Project No. AFA-1-F117/F118 (Box 142)
    - WDTA Project No. AFA-1-F142 Commandant's Headquarters (Box 142)
    - Projects AFA-1-G 113 & P134. Cadet Quarters Complex. Agenda- Presentation of Preliminaries. 14 Sept. 56 & Equipment List by Sub Agency and Room (Box 142)
    - Projects AFA-1-G113 & P134. Cadet Quarters Complex. Agenda. Presentation of Preliminaries 14 September 56 & Equipment List by Sub Agency and Room (Box 142)
    - Projects AFA-3-P-133 & P-136. Cadet Social Complex. Agenda. Presentation of Preliminaries (Revised). 28 Feb 57 & Equipment List by Sub Agency and Room (Box 142)
    - Procurement Data Sheets (Box 142)
    - Laverne - M. Aiden, Miscellaneous (Box 143)
    - Receiving Tickets - AFA-1-A (Box 143)
    - AFA- Logs (Received in, shipped out NY) obsolete (Box 143)
    - Clocks (Box 143)
    - Apr-58 (Box 143)
    - May-58 (Box 144)
    - Doormats (Box 144)
    - Jul-58 (Box 144)
    - Aug-58 (Box 144)
    - Sep-58 (Box 144)
    - AFA - Denver - Conf. Reports, memos, etc. To and from. 3/15 to 6/30/56 (Box 144)
    - AFA - Denver - Conference Reports, memos. From 7/1/56 to 10/15/56. Folder #2 (Box 145)
    - AFA correspondence with client 1959 (Box 145)
    - Standard Procedure File (Box 145)
    - Emeco (Box 145)
    - Blair (Box 145)
    - J.G. Furniture Co. Walnut Chairs (Box 145)
    - TL (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Mill End Drapery Shop (Box 146)
    - Mill End Drapery Shop (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - McKee, General Contractor, Inc., Robert E. (Box 146)
    - Metalab Equipment Company (Box 146)
    - Mosler Safe Company (Box 146)
    - Mutual Furniture and Fixture Co. (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Polar Ware Company (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Remington Rand Revision (Box 146)
    - Red Circle Display Case Company (Box 146)
    - Vendors (Box 146)
    - Reeves-Keeton-Ryan, Inc. (Box 147)
    - Systems Sales Co. (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Blair Aluminum Furniture Company (Box 147)
    - Thonet Industries, Inc. (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Federal Prison Industries, Inc. (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Gem Metal Specialties, Inc. (Box 147)
    - Cal-Ohm Laboratories, Inc. (Box 147)
    - Cardwell Blueprint & Supply co. (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Cole Furniture and Equipment Company (Box 147)
    - Vendors (Box 147)
    - Desks, Inc (Box 148)
    - Detroit Lectern Company, Inc. (Box 148)
    - Drexel Furniture Company (Box 148)
    - Vendors (Box 148)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 148)
    - Huntington Chair Corporation Shop Drawings (Box 148)
    - Huntington Chair Corporation (Box 149)
    - Hermsdorf Fixture Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box 149)
    - Horblit and Company (Box 149)
    - Harbison-Paine, Inc. (Box 149)
    - Harris-Hub Company (Box 149)
    - Hosek Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box 149)
    - Hallack & Howard Lumber Co. (Box 149)
    - Bro-Dart Industries (Box 149)
    - Brabrook Inc. (Box 149)
    - Vendors (Box 149)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 149)
    - Vendors (Box 149)
    - L&L Furniture Company (Box 149)
    - Jarvis & Jarvis, Inc. (Box 149)
    - Phineas Juster (Box 149)
    - Juster, Phineas (Box 149)
    - Jiffy Join Incorporated (Box 149)
    - Vendors (Box 149)
    - Vendors (Box 150)
    - Legion Utensils Co. (Box 150)
    - Laurel Lamp Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box 150)
    - Ludwig & Patterson, Co. (Box 150)
    - Lyon Metal Products, Incorporated (Box 150)
    - Hosek Manufacturing Co (Box 150)
    - Tables (Conference) (Box 150)
    - Dining Table (Box 150)
    - Desk, 250 Man lecture halt (Box 150)
    - Balance Table (Box 150)
    - 15" Seat Height Alum. Frame Chair (Box 150)
    - Tables (w/pedestal) (Box 150)
    - Swivels (Box 150)
    - Thonet Ind. (Box 150)
    - AFA Phase 2, Phase 3 (Box 150)
    - Sciences Building, Humanities Building (Box 151)
    - Cadet Natorium, Cadet Gymnasium (Box 151)
    - Airbase Group Headquarters, Security Force (Box 151)
    - Communications Building (Box 151)
    - Television (Box 151)
    - Commandants Headquarters (Box 151)
    - Cadet Theatre Organ (Box 151)
    - Staff Club P117 (Box 151)
    - WDTA Progress Reports and Time Schedules (Box 151)
    - BOQ-VOQ AFA-3 G111 (Box 152)
    - Tables & Benches (Box 152)
    - Chairs, Wood; Leather Upholstered (Box 152)
    - Bookcase, Cadet Room (Box 152)
    - Chairs (Box 152)
    - Store Fixtures (Box 152)
    - 18" Seat Height Walnut Frame Open Arm Chairs (Box 152)
    - Cadet Room Desk (Box 152)
    - Amendment # 2 for 18" Seat Height Alum. Chairs (Box 152)
    - Cabinet, Serving (Box 152)
    - Theater Curtain (Box 152)
    - Base Exchange (Box 152)
    - Cadet Social Center Complex Color and Material Schedule (Box 152)
    - Conference Notes (Box 152)
    - Cadet Store (Box 152)
    - Outgoing Correspondence (Box 152)
    - Base Exchange Comp. P112 - Post Exchange, R932 - Commissary, RR313 - Clothing Sales, P121 - Bowling Alley, P116 - Service Club, P113 - Academy Theatre (Box 152)
    - Spitz Planetarium R-932, AFA-3 (Box 152)
    - Support Pers. Din. Hall G122 AFA-3 (Box 152)
    - Projects AFA-1-F-141 (&P381) Superintendent's Headquarters. Agenda" Presentation of Preliminaries 12 Dec 56 (Box 153)
    - Bookcases, Cabinets, and Desk (Box 153)
    - Desk: Component Assemblies (Box 153)
    - Fabric Memos (Box 153)
    - Air Force Academy Casement Cloth "Dacron" (Box 153)
    - Projects AFA-1-G-113 & P134. Cadet Quarters Complex Agenda. Presentation of Preliminaries 14 Sept. 56 (Box 153)
    - 7 (Box 153)
    - Cadet Quarters G113-000 (Box 154)
    - Petty Cash Chicago Office (Box 154)
    - Miscellaneous Furnishings (Box 154)
    - Rugs and Carpets (Box 154)
    - Library Furn. (Box 154)
    - Couch, upholstery (Box 154)
    - Molded plastic chair (Box 154)
    - Molded Plastic Chair, Rotary (Box 154)
    - AFA-1 General - All jobs (Box 154)
    - Color and Material Schedules Air Force Academy Construction Agency (Box 155)
    - General Correspondence (Box 155)
    - Partition (Box 155)
    - Library F-111-000 (Box 155)
    - Huntington AFA-13 Benches and Tables (Box 155)
    - Room Color Schedule for Cadet Social Center Complex (Box 155)
    - Standing Operating Procedure, Room Arrangement. Headquarters, US Corps of Cadets (Box 155)
    - Ludwig and Patterson 636 (Box 155)
    - Family Housing (Box 155)
    - Fabric & Cloth, Curtains WTD (Box 156)
    - Shipping & Receiving (Box 156)
    - Products (Box 156)
    - Cadet Social Center Complex Color and Materials Schedule (Box 156)
    - Color and Material Schedule (Box 156)
    - Color Schedules (Box 157)
    - Cadet Social Complex Agenda (Box 157)
    - Academic Complex (Box 157)
    - Specifications - racks, hat and Coat (Box 158)
    - Cadet Dining Hall Equipment (Box 158)
    - Correspondence Re; Dining Halls, Folder # 2, M. Aiden (Box 158)
    - Dwg. No. 5 (Box 158)
    - Academic Comp F-117, F-118 (Box 159)
    - Procedure and Schedule Data (Box 159)
    - Day Book (Box 160)
    - 2.Phase III Preliminaries - Equipment Lists, etc. (Box 160)
    - 2 unlabeled black binders (Box 161)
    - unlabeled (Box 162)
    - Day Book, 1957 Jan/June (Box 162)
    - IFBs (Box 163)
    - Day Book, July-November 1957 (Box 163)
    - Trans. Ltrs. (Box 164)
    - Day Book, Jan, Feb, March 1958 (Box 164)
    - Drawing Numbers (Box 165)
    - Phase I Preliminaries (Box 165)
    - Procure Data - carts & misc machines (Box 166)
    - RD-5 Sterilizer Test Data (Box 166)
    - AFA Spec Data (Box 166)
    - Procurement Data Jan 16 1958 Eleanor Way AFA 2A (Box 167)
    - Memos and Notes E. Way (Box 167)
    - Specifications AFA-2A (Box 167)
    - General Info - AFA Academy (Box 168)
    - Procurement Data Library E. Way (Box 168)
    - Procurement Data. E. Way (Box 168)
    - Unlabeled (Box 168)
    - Cadet Quarters Sample Cover (Box 169)
    - COC F-142 (Box 169)
    - unlabeled binder - diagrams (Box 169)
    - C.O.C. office copy (Box 170)
    - 4A 3500 NLR 6620100 to 6921 NLR 1104500 (Box 170)
    - 3A Complete Numerical Listing - NLR Original Office Copy (Box 170)
    - Unlabeled binder - diagrams (Box 171)
    - 2A Complete Numerical Listing - NLR - Ok'd with Flimel AC EW Correct and prices entered (Box 171)
    - 2A Complete Numerical Listing NLR - OK'd with Flimel, AC EW Correct and prices entered (Box 171)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog - Cadet Quarters Complex Cadet Dining Hall (Box 172)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog (Box 172)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog - Racks, Stacks, Shelving, Stands, Bookcases (Box 172)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog - Filing Copy (Box 172)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog (Box 173)
    - US Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog (Box 173)
    - Dummy for Dining Hall (Box 173)
    - Diagrams (Box 173)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Dining Hall. Project AFA-1-G121 Equipment Catalog, March 15, 1957. (Box 174)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Dining Hall Project AFA-1-G121 Equipment Catalog, May 17, 1957 (Box 174)
    - United States Air Force Academy Superintendent's Headquarters Project AFA-1-F-141 & AFA-1-P-381. Equipment Catalog April 18, 1957 (Box 174)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Social Center Complex. Project AFA-3-P133 & AFA-3-P136. Equipment Catalog May 13, 1957. (Box 174)
    - United States Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog. Superintendent's Headquarters. Filing Copy (Box 175)
    - United States Air Force Academy. Equipment Catalog. Superintendent's Headquarters. (Box 175)
    - United States Air Force Academy. Equipment Catalog. Academic Complex, Commandant's Headquarters (Box 175)
    - United States Air Force Academy. Equipment Catalog (Box 175)
    - United States Air Force Academy Equipment Catalog (Box 176)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Social Center Complex Project AFA-3-P133 & AFA-3-P136 Equipment Catalog. May 13, 1957 (Box 176)
    - United States Air Force Academy Academic Complex Project AFA-1-F-111 & AFA-1-F-442 (Box 176)
    - Academic Complex (Box 177)
    - Cadet Quarters, Cadet Store (Box 177)
    - United States Air Force Academy Superintendent's Headquarters Project AFA-1-F-141 & AFA-1-P-381 Equipment Catalog April 18, 1957 (Box 177)
    - Specifications (Box 178)
    - Utility Connected Items. Cat. Tabulation (Box 178)
    - Utility Connected Items. Cat. Tabulation (Box 178)
    - United States Air Force Academy Academic Complex. Project AFA-1-F-111 & AFA-1-F-142, AFA-1-F-117 & AFA-1-F-118. Equipment Catalog April 5, 1957 (Box 178)
    - Specifications (Box 179)
    - Cadet Quarters, Cadet Store (Box 179)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Dispensary Project AFA-3-M-113. Equipment Catalog July 22, 1957 (Box 179)
    - Cadet Dispensary AFA-3-M-113.000 (Box 179)
    - Cadet Dispensary AFA-3-M-113.000 (Box 179)
    - Cadet Dispensary (Box 179)
    - BOQ-VOQ (Box 179)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 1 of 6 (Box 180)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 2 of 6 (Box 180)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 3 of 56 (Box 180)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 4 of 6 (Box 181)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 5 of 6 (Box 181)
    - Discontinued Drawings Vol. 6 of 6 (Box 181)
    - United States Air Force Academy Cadet Quarters and Cadet Store Project AFA-1-G113 & AFA-1-P134. Equipment Catalog March 26, 1957 (Box 182)
    - Comparative List Stock Numbers (Box 182)
    - Big wooden rubber stamps (Box 182)
- Miscellaneous
  - Proceedings, Art Directors' Club, 1925 (Box 1)
  - Artists Guild Membership Card (Box 1)
  - Awards, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Articles about Teague from "The Printing Art" or "The American Printer", 1917; 1919,; 1921,; 1923,; 1924,; 1926 (Box 1)
    "Some recent examples of decorative design and lettering done by Walter Dorwin Teague" in The Printing Art, March 1917
    "An Artistic Series of Advertisements" in The Printing Art, November 1919
    Decorative display card designed by Teague, in The American Printer, September 20, 1921
    "The Use of Ornament with Garamond, Caslon, and Bodoni Types" in The American Printer, December 20, 1923
    "The Use of Ornament with Caslon Types" in The American Printer, January 20, 1924
    "Ornament with Bodoni Types" in The American Printer, February 20, 1924 [IMPERFECT]
    Cover illustration in The American Printer, February 5, 1926
    "The Circuit Rider" illustration designed by Teague, in The American Printer, July 1926
  - Catalog Cuts - Conimercial Items (chairs, etc) (Box 1)
  - Catalog Cuts - Commercial Items (Box 1)
  - Procurement Data Sheets, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Seating Study, Diagrams, sketches, subject information, objectives, notes (Box 1)
  - Spec. Format, Military specifications, federal specifications, etc (Box 1)
  - Travel Expenses, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Articles about Mr. Teague (Box 1)
    Design Trends
    Design for Industry
    Industrial Design
    Unattributed articles
    U.S. Steel Advertisement
    Harcourt, Brace News
    Hundterdon County Democrat
    The Hundterton Republic
  - Biography of Mr. Teague: "Walter Dorwin Teague: Dean of Design - a portrait." Printers' Ink magazine, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Chrysler Corp. Conference Reports (Box 1)
  - General Dynamics Conference Reports (Box 1)
  - Cows, Damaged negatives of cow illustrations (Box 1)
  - Photographs - portraits of Mr. Teague (Box 1)
  - World's Fair materials, photographs, etc (Box 1)
  - Eastern Kodak - advertising package (Box 1)
- Oversize material
  - Air Force Academy construction drawings (Oversize 1)
  - Air Force Academy construction drawings (Oversize 2)
  - Air Force Academy construction drawings (Oversize 3)
  - Air Force Academy construction drawings (Oversize 4)
  - Air Force Academy construction drawings (Oversize 5)
  - Source material, other artists original and reproduced work; Les Arabesques by Watteau removed for separate cataloging. (Oversize 6)
  - Printing and lettering, French and Spanish manuscripts (replicas) (Oversize 7)
  - Universal Paleography or Fac-Similes of Writings, Vol. 1, by M.J. B. Silvestre, Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging. (Oversize 8)
  - Universal Paleography or Fac-Similes of Writings, Vol. 2, by M.J. B. Silvestre, Transferred to Rare Books for separate cataloging. (Oversize 9)
  - Designs - architectural (Oversize 10)
  - Illustrations, seals, logos, book/article illustrations (Oversize 11)
  - Illustrations, large-sized colored design posters, design sketches, poster "Exhibition of Recent Work by Walter Dorwin Teacgue," colored posters of illustrated images of people, etc, "Fourth Annual Horse Show" poster, colored mounted invitations, posters advertising events (Oversize 12)
  - Layouts, advertising, cigarettes, clothing, accessories, pianos, utensils (Oversize 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Layouts, advertising; Teague's original sketches, miscellaneous drawings; Kodak, Atwater Kent, Chesterfield, Tudor Plate, Fatima, Autopiano Company, Hoffman, Newell-Emmett Company, Sec, Shreve Crump and Low, Adler-Rochester, Community Plate, Bulova Watches, etc (Oversize 14)
  - Illustration borders, "Art in Buttons," mounted borders, border sketches, music notes, "Women's Home Companion," etc (Oversize 15)
  - Layouts, printing, alphabet, layout, designs, fonts, engraving company sheets, samples, advertisements, etc (Oversize 16)
  - Pencil sketches, Libby Owens designs, Cadillac, illustration of man on horseback, Chesterfield, cigarettes, Locomobile, illustrations of Roman-style pillars, portraits, nudes (Oversize 17)
  - Products, sketches, illustrations, mounted sketches, colored sketches, illustrations of human figures, vases, colored jars, etc (Oversize 18A)
  - Products, sketches, illustrations, cars, colors, design pattern notes, human figures, vending machines, American Gas Association color illustrations, cups, vases, shapes (Oversize 18B)
  - Drawings/sketches, large color drawings/sketches of chairs, airplane seats, cars (Oversize 18C)
  - Product labels, Albers & c/s stats, Canadian Oil Refineries Limited, Motorine Motor Oil, Conoco, White Rose, Continental Oil Company (Oversize 19)
  - Product labels, black and white photographs, American Cyanamid Company, dimensions, paper "Application of Cyanamid Trademark to Plants, Plant Facilities, and Branch Offices" (Oversize 20)
  - Product packaging, labels, product packaging (Aero Cyanamid Pulverized, Aluminum Sulfate, Calcium Carbonate, Iron Blue, Chrome Yellow, Chrome Green, Unitane), printed labels (spot remover, household oil, lighter fluid), mounted package samples (Megasul 25%, Cyanamid, Aero Calcium Carbonat, Chrome Green, Unitane, Tobias Acid, MBT, Aluminum Sulfate) (Oversize 21)
  - Miscellaneous, Gorham kitchenware catalog, constructive criticism graphs - airline designs, miscellaneous (Oversize 22)
  - Scrapbook of Henry Mattson news clippings, 1923-1945; Transferred to Henry Mattson Collection
  - DNA molecule model, 1962 (Oversize 23)
  - Model cash register, National Cash Register Company (Oversize 24)